haggle.com 2010-11-20

# BigDeal.com Customer Service : Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

BigDeal provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of [bigdeal.com](http://www.bigdeal.com/). This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through this Site.  This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time.  We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site.  You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our BigDeal [Terms of Service](http://support.bigdeal.com/forums/84207/entries/76568).

As used in this policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally.  

Information Collection and Use

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Site, services, features and content, to administer your Membership (together, the “Service”) and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site.  

Personally Identifiable Information.  

o When you register with us through the Site, as a BigDeal Subscriber or when you choose to create your own profile webpage we will ask you for personally identifiable information.  This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Information”).  Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, username, phone number, credit card or other billing information, email address and home and business postal addresses, and any other information that you decide to add to your profile webpage.  We use your Personal Information mainly to provide the Service and administer your inquiries. 

o We also collect the other information that you provide as part of registration and the administration and personalization of the My Account webpage (e.g., without limitation, zip code (on its own) and individual preferences) (“Non-Identifying Information”).

o We use your Personal Information (in some cases, in conjunction with your Non-Identifying Information) mainly to provide the Service, complete your transactions, and administer your inquiries.   

o We may also collect information regarding your activity on the Site, such as your bidding history, auctions participated in, auctions won/lost, prices paid, bids used and other similar information associated with your username. We use such information solely in accordance with this Privacy Policy

o Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers (for example, combining your zip code with your street address) in a way that enables you to be identified.  But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other non-identifying information (for example, your viewing preferences).  We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other BigDeal Users (defined below) to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Service and to analyze and understand how our Site and Service are used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically, for instance to deliver a product to you according to your preferences or restrictions.

We also use your Personal Information to contact you with BigDeal newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you.  If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or update your “user preferences” information. (See “Changing or Deleting Information,” below.) 

o Log Data.  When you visit the Site, whether as a BigDeal Subscriber or a non-registered user just browsing (any of these, a “BigDeal User”), our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”).  This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Site, pages of our Site that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Site, access times and dates, and other statistics.  We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Site and the Service and for the Site’s technical administration, to increase our Site’s functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor it to our visitors’ needs.  For example, some of this information is collected so that when you visit the Site again, it will recognize you and serve advertisements and other information appropriate to your interests.  We also use this information to verify that visitors to the Site meet the criteria required to process their requests.  [We do not treat Log Data as Personal Information or use it in association with other Personal Information, though we may aggregate, analyze and evaluate such information for the same purposes as stated above regarding other Non-Identifying Information.]

Cookies

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information.  A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes.  We use cookies for two purposes.  First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your registration ID for future logins to the Site.  Second, we utilize persistent ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor aggregate usage by BigDeal Users and web traffic routing on the Site. Third party advertisers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your browser.  You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.  If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Service.  

Emailing Via a BigDeal Account

As part of the Service, BigDeal Subscribers may choose to communicate with BigDeal Subscribers and non-registered users through use of their accounts.  Where BigDeal Subscribers have selected the option of adding one or more email addresses to an online form, the message they create in the corresponding template will be sent from BigDeal to those email addresses on their behalf.  These email addresses will be stored in the address book the BigDeal Subscriber creates and will be used only for the purpose of sending the email communication to the addressee.  

Inviting Friends Via a BigDeal Account

As part of the Service, we may allow BigDeal Subscribers to invite friends to participate in BigDeal service. When BigDeal Subscribers have selected the option of adding one or more email addresses to an online form or via an address book import, the resulting invites will be sent to those email addresses on their behalf.  These email addresses will be stored in the import friends function that BigDeal creates and will be used only for the purpose of sending the email invite to the addressee(s) selected by the BigDeal Subscribers. 

Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as “phishing” are of great concern to BigDeal.  Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority.  We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.  For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

**BigDeal Users**.  When you register through the Site and submit your Personal Information to create a profile webpage, BigDeal Users will see your “Screen Name” and the month and year you first registered with BigDeal (“Required Subscriber Identifiers”). You can choose what other Personal Information you provide as part of your profile (“Other Subscriber Information”) and in some cases you can choose whether to share that information publicly on the Site by making selections via the “user preferences” section of your profile webpage.  Providing Other Subscriber Information is voluntary and should correlate with the degree of interaction you want to have with BigDeal Users. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and that you not use your real name as your “Screen Name,” since that would allow others to identify you.  

**Auction Data and Bidding History.**   We may share information on your bidding history, auctions participated in, auctions won/lost, prices paid, bids used and other similar information associated with your username, for the purpose of providing BigDeal Users with information designed to help in the formulation of bidding strategies, in accordance with the options selected by you when creating your user account and profile. 

**Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information**.  We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

**Service Providers**.  We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Site-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, fulfillment, web analytics and improvement of the Site’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and Service are used.  These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. [We may also provide Personal Information to our business partners or other trusted entities for the purpose of providing you with information on goods or services we believe will be of interest to you.  You can, at any time, opt out of receiving such communications.]

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement.**   BigDeal cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law.  We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of BigDeal or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. 

**Business Transfers.**   BigDeal may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

Changing or Deleting Your Information

All Subscribers may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their registration profile by contacting us.  If you completely delete all such information, then your account may become deactivated.  If you would like us to delete your record in our system, use the “Close My Account” function in My Account [provide link]. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request.  We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. 

Security 

BigDeal is very concerned with safeguarding your information.  We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored “personal data” (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction.  If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, BigDeal transfers Personal Information to the United States and processes it there.  Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Links to Other Sites

Our Site contains links to other websites.  If you choose to visit an advertiser by “clicking on” a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website.  The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices.  We do not exercise control over third party websites.  These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. They may also use JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them.  We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.  

Our Policy Toward Children

This Site is not directed to children under 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should [contact us](http://support.bigdeal.com/requests/anonymous/new). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.  

Contacting Us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://support.bigdeal.com/requests/anonymous/new).
